<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Haoran You</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Haoran You</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 20:40:26 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hermann Park</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hermann_park/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 20:40:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hermann_park/</guid>
      <description>Before applying for Ph.D., I heard that Rice University is of highest happiness index. I assured this is the case for undergraduates while not applied to Ph.D. students since environment makes no difference for those living in office (XD). However today&amp;rsquo;s impromptu visit to the neighbor &amp;ldquo;Hermann Park&amp;rdquo; while I was waiting for the food delivery at nightfall almost changes my mind.
Go out of the school and cross the road to the riverside in the park, I sat on a bench by the river and watched all kinds of people go by, like an old man but not wise enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[ICLR 2020] Drawing Early-Bird Tickets: Towards More Efficient Training of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publication/early-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:03:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publication/early-bird/</guid>
      <description>Accepted as spotlight oral paper! Abstract: (Frankle &amp;amp; Carbin, 2019) shows that there exist winning tickets (small but critical subnetworks) for dense, randomly initialized networks, that can be trained alone to achieve comparable accuracies to the latter in a similar number of iterations. However, the identification of these winning tickets still requires the costly train-prune-retrain process, limiting their practical benefits. In this paper, we discover for the first time that the winning tickets can be identified at the very early training stage, which we term as early-bird (EB) tickets, via low-cost training schemes (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is first post!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haoran You (游浩然)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bio/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bio/intro/</guid>
      <description> Research Experience  Graduate Student at Rice University (2019 - Present) Undergraduate Student at Huazhong University of Science and Technology (2015 - 2019)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>