<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lottery Ticket Hypothesis on Haoran You</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/lottery-ticket-hypothesis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lottery Ticket Hypothesis on Haoran You</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 15:24:07 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/lottery-ticket-hypothesis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lottery Ticket Hypothesis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/lottery-ticket/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 15:24:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/lottery-ticket/</guid>
      <description>Lottery Ticket Hypothesis  A randomly-initialized, dense neural network contains a subnetwork that is initialized such that—when trained in isolation—it can match the test accuracy of the original network after training for at most the same number of iterations.  
Recent Surge  Drawing Early-Bird Tickets: Towards More Efficient Training of Neural Networks:  Discover for the first time that the winning tickets can be identified at the very early training stage, which we term as early-bird (EB) tickets, via low-cost training schemes (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[ICLR 2020] Drawing Early-Bird Tickets: Towards More Efficient Training of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publication/early-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:03:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publication/early-bird/</guid>
      <description>Accepted as spotlight oral paper! Abstract: (Frankle &amp;amp; Carbin, 2019) shows that there exist winning tickets (small but critical subnetworks) for dense, randomly initialized networks, that can be trained alone to achieve comparable accuracies to the latter in a similar number of iterations. However, the identification of these winning tickets still requires the costly train-prune-retrain process, limiting their practical benefits. In this paper, we discover for the first time that the winning tickets can be identified at the very early training stage, which we term as early-bird (EB) tickets, via low-cost training schemes (e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>