<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Haoran You</title>
    <link>http://localhost:52834/publication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Haoran You</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:03:59 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:52834/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[NeurIPS 2020] ShiftAddNet: A Hardware-Inspired Deep Network </title>
      <link>http://localhost:52834/publication/shiftaddnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:03:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:52834/publication/shiftaddnet/</guid>
      <description>Accepted as NeurIPS 2020 regular paper! Abstract: Multiplication (e.g., convolution) is arguably a cornerstone of modern deep neural networks (DNNs). However, intensive multiplications cause expensive resource costs that challenge DNN deployment on resource-constrained edge devices, driving several attempts for multiplication-less deep networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[NeurIPS 2020] FracTrain: Fractionally Squeezing Bit Savings Both Temporally and Spatially for Efficient DNN Training </title>
      <link>http://localhost:52834/publication/fractrain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:03:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:52834/publication/fractrain/</guid>
      <description>Accepted as NeurIPS 2020 regular paper! Abstract: Recent breakthroughs in deep neural networks (DNNs) have fueled a tremendous demand for intelligent edge devices featuring on-site learning, while the practical realization of such systems remains a challenge due to the limited resources available at the edge and the required massive training costs for state-of-the-art (SOTA) DNNs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[ECCV 2020] HALO: Hardware-Aware Learning to Optimize</title>
      <link>http://localhost:52834/publication/l2o/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 18:03:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:52834/publication/l2o/</guid>
      <description>Accepted as ECCV 2020 regular paper! Abstract: There has been an explosive demand for bringing machine learning (ML) powered intelligence into numerous Internet-of-Things (IoT) devices. However, the effectiveness of such intelligent functionality requires in-situ continuous model adaptation for adapting to new data and environments, while the on-device computing and energy resources are usually extremely constrained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[ISCA 2020] SmartExchange: Trading Higher-cost Memory Storage/Access for Lower-cost Computation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:52834/publication/smart-exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 18:03:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:52834/publication/smart-exchange/</guid>
      <description>Accepted as ISCA 2020 regular paper! Abstract: We present SmartExchange, an algorithm-hardware co-design framework to trade higher-cost memory storage/access for lower-cost computation, for energy-efficient inference of deep neural networks (DNNs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[ICLR 2020] Drawing Early-Bird Tickets: Towards More Efficient Training of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:52834/publication/early-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:03:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:52834/publication/early-bird/</guid>
      <description>Accepted as spotlight oral paper! Abstract: (Frankle &amp;amp; Carbin, 2019) shows that there exist winning tickets (small but critical subnetworks) for dense, randomly initialized networks, that can be trained alone to achieve comparable accuracies to the latter in a similar number of iterations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[IEEE TNNLS] Bayesian Cycle-Consistent Generative Adversarial Networks via Marginalizing Latent Sampling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:52834/publication/bayesian-cyclegan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:03:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:52834/publication/bayesian-cyclegan/</guid>
      <description>Accepted as IEEE TNNLS regular paper! Abstract: Recent techniques built on generative adversarial networks (GANs), such as cycle-consistent GANs, are able to learn mappings among different domains built from unpaired data sets, through min-max optimization games between generators and discriminators.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>